(Sheldon:)Everything's going to change.
(Sheldon:)Howard won't be able
to come over as much.
(Raj:)Well, he could bring the baby here.
Oh, but then we'd have to
(Sheldon:)baby-proof the apartment.
You know, my sister
(Sheldon:)has one of those toilet locks
in her bathroom.
(Sheldon:)I have two doctorates,
I still had to go in the sink.
(Howard:)Oh, my God,
and do you have any idea
(Howard:)how expensive having a kid is?
(Raj:)I read that in Los Angeles,
raising a child through college
(Raj:)can cost over a million dollars.
(Howard:)A million dollars?
(Howard:)God, it's like my nuts
just kicked me in the nuts.
(Howard:)That's it... I got to start
(Howard:)earning more money right now.
(Bernadette:)I know...
you could ask Bernadette
(Raj:)for a raise in your allowance.
(Howard:)This isn't a joke.
(Raj:)I wasn't joking.
(Leonard:)It'll be fine.
(Leonard:)People have kids every day.
(Leonard:)You'll figure this out.
Yeah, come on,
(Raj:)this is great news
and you know it.
Oh... You're right, it is,
(Howard:)I'm just...
a little overwhelmed right now.
(Leonard:)Hey, you know what we should do?